spoonyexperiment.com 2013-06-28

# The Spoony Experiment Privacy Policy » The Spoony Experiment

## [Privacy Policy](http://spoonyexperiment.com/privacy-policy-2/ "Permanent Link to Privacy Policy")

This privacy policy sets out how “The Spoony Experiment” uses and protects any information that you give “The Spoony Experiment” when you use this website.

“The Spoony Experiment” is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

“The Spoony Experiment” may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from September 1, 2012.

**What we collect**  
We may collect the following information:  
* name  
* birthdate  
* city/state of the user’s current location  
* contact information including email address and social media identification for sites such as ICQ, AIM, MSN, YIM, Steam, XBox Live, MySpace, Facebook, Twitter, and others.  
* IP address and hostname used when logging in  
* demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests  
* other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

This site may leverage the use of third party advertising technology, that could include the collection of data relevant to reporting and/or targeting activities. Other technologies (such as cookies, javascript, or web beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see. We have no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you would like an opportunity to opt out from such collection and use, please go to the following link and opt out: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**What we do with the information we gather**  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:  
* Internal record keeping.  
* We may use the information to improve our products and services.  
* We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  
* We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.  
* We may provide your information to our third party partners for marketing or promotional purposes.  
* We will never sell your information.

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on SpoonyExperiment.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit here and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

**Links to other websites**  
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Log Files**  
Like many other websites, we make use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information, are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us as soon as possible, at [spoonyone@spoonyexperiment.com.](mailto:spoony%6f%6e%65%40sp%6f%6f%6ey%65x%70%65r%69m%65%6e%74.c%6fm%2e) We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
